http://imm.edu/privacy-pollicy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyInternational Media Ministries vision is that the good news of Jesus will be available to every person, on every screen. We work with missionaries, national churches and media outlets, and communicate with them regarding this work we do producing media content and training others to use media. We communicate to share media resources, training opportunities, and general information regarding IMM. We also communicate with constituency in Europe, the USA, and beyond who want to pray for and support IMM. We desire to communicate with all these people regularly and legally.You receive contact from us because you have connected with IMM in a venue, on the website, with our team or on email and wanted to stay informed of our work. Your contact details are kept securely on our database solely for the purpose of informing you of our work, fundraising needs, and prayer requests. The information is not shared with other organizations. Each email you receive from us via MailChimp enables you to update your information or unsubscribe. You can also contact us at info@imm.edu if you want to change any of your preferences.IMM is committed to the protection of your personal information that you entrust to us as we spread the good news to others using media.En virtud de lo dispuesto en la Ley Orgánica 3/2018, de 5 de diciembre, de Protección de Datos Personales y Garantía de los Derechos Digitales (LODGDD) y en el Reglamento (UE) 2016/679 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo de 27 de abril de 2016 relativo a la protección de las personas físicas en lo que respecta al tratamiento de datos personales y a la libre circulación de estos datos (RGPD), le informamos de que sus datos de carácter personal recogidos de fuentes accesibles al público o datos que usted nos ha facilitado previamente, proceden de un fichero propiedad de INTERNATIONAL MEDIA MINISTRIES
con la finalidad de gestionar la relación de negocio que nos vincula e informarle de nuestros productos y servicios. Puede ejercitar los derechos de acceso, rectificación, supresión, portabilidad de sus datos, de limitación y oposición a su tratamiento dirigiéndose por escrito al Responsable en Protección de Datos de INTERNATIONAL MEDIA MINISTRIES
en C/ Pablo Picasso, 10, 28810-Los Hueros- Madrid, o al correo electrónico connect@imm.edu Le informamos que, de acuerdo con lo dispuesto en la Ley 34/2002, de 11 de julio, de Servicios de la Sociedad de la Información y del Comercio Electrónico, si no desea recibir más información sobre los servicios que ofrecemos puede enviar un mensaje con la palabra “BAJA”, a la siguiente dirección de correo electrónico: connect@imm.edu El contenido de este correo electrónico y sus anexos son estrictamente confidenciales. En caso de no ser usted el destinatario y haber recibido este mensaje por error, agradeceríamos que lo comunique inmediatamente al remitente sin difundir, almacenar o copiar su contenido y le rogamos proceda a su destrucción.
